Guide to the John F. Manley Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
John F. Manley papers
1946-2000
1983-2000
SC0428
Manley, John F.
5 Linear feet
Clippings, press releases, statements, memoranda, correspondence, petitions, and other papers pertaining to the relationship between Stanford University and the Hoover Institution, the proposed Ronald Reagan Presidential Library at Stanford, working conditions for farmworkers on Webb Ranch (located on Stanford lands), Stanford presidents Donald Kennedy and Gerhard Casper, University Provost Condoleezza Rice, and other political issues.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of John Manley, 1992 and 2001.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Professor of political science at Stanford University.
Description of the Collection
Clippings, press releases, statements, memoranda, correspondence, petitions, and other papers pertaining to the relationship between Stanford University and the Hoover Institution, the proposed Ronald Reagan Presidential Library at Stanford, working conditions for farmworkers on Webb Ranch (located on Stanford lands), Stanford presidents Donald Kennedy and Gerhard Casper, University Provost Condoleezza Rice, and other political issues.
Access Terms
Hoover Institution on War, Revolution, and Peace; Kennedy, Donald, 1931-; Manley, John F.; Migrant agricultural laborers--California.; Presidents--United States--Archives.
Collection Contents
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2001-206
  - Additional clippings, letters, internet printouts, etc., re:
    - Hoover Institution / Pres. Casper / C. Rice – 1 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Hoover Institution / Pres. Casper / C. Rice – 2 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Hoover Institution / Pres. Casper / C. Rice – 3 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Web Ranch – 1 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Web Ranch – 2 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Web Ranch – 3 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2003-333
  - Corruption of Stanford, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Coe Endowment/Hoover, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Kennedy, Donald, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Webb Ranch/Scotty McLennan, 1989, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Why Stanford is not a great university, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)